One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was a crybaby
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
The word "thank you" has faded into the wind now
Am I getting stronger?
I don't know the answer yet
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
So let's go
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to lose something precious
The voice inside of me
keeps sustaining me
Wicked rain will get in my way
But I won't walk away
So let's go
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to lose something precious
To the future I believe in...
Navy Headquarters
It looks like you barely managed to hold on to your lives.
If I hadn't shown up with the antidote...
Impel Down
you'd all be dead by now.
You underestimated Magellan.
We're still alive!
You were... destined to come here.
Well, I really thought we were going to die.
Seems like we...
got lucky this time.
Heaven chooses who survives,
but if you give up, you've already lost!
Might as well live in the moment.
Hey, Shiryu!
It was nice of you to save us. Thanks a lot.
I welcome you once again.
You'll make a fine addition to our crew!
I have no future here.
I was hoping to meet a man like you.
The World Government's Private Route: The Tarai Current
Let vus rest Inazuma here.
Huh? You mean the poison has affected him that badly?
Vi was able to treat the poison he hit vme with,
using vmy Healing and Tension Hormones...
But that technique has some nasty side effects.
It can even shorten your lifespan.
It'd be better for him to recuperate naturally.
Once vyour lifespan has been shortened, vyou'll never be able to reclaim the years vyou've lost.
Inazuma is an important newkama to the Revolutionary Army.
He shouldn't overexert himself now.
You know, he wasn't such a bad guy, after all.
We just reunited,
and he's gone and saved me again!
Bon-chan!
Brother Bon!
Hey, how long're you guys
gonna stand 'round sobbin' for?
He was a good guy but he's dead now.
Let's just celebrate!
Celebrate our freedom!
Or, if you'd like, we could make it a wake for Mr. 2.
What a bloody nice service!
Bon-chan could still be alive, big-nose!
Who're you callin' big-nose?!
You, you red-nosed, round-nosed, stupid-nosed idiot!
Well, you've got a rubbery, stretchy, stupid face!
What'd you say?!
Oh, just do whatever the hell you want.
I thought only Merfolk were able to talk to fish.
I'm surprised you were able to summon whale sharks.
What's odd about a fishman being on
good terms with sea creatures?
It's just odd.
I mean, for such a savage race...
I suppose you're an exception.
Well, I'll take that as a compliment.
I can't deny that Fishmen are savage.
Bon-chan isn't dead!
Captain Buggy got a second red nose!
Luffy-kun.
Thanks to you, I have a chance to help with rescuing Ace-san.
I'm indebted to you.
Oh, don't mention it.
Besides, I'm glad you're with us. You're really strong!
This isn't the first time I've been indebted to you.
I should express my gratitude and apologies but...
we must focus on our current objective.
You can call me Jinbe!
I used to be one of the Seven Warlords, but I've abandoned that title!
Let's unleash hell at Navy HQ!
We must save Ace-san,
so that Okama-kun's efforts won't go to waste!
A warlord?
Navy HQ?
Huh?!
Hey, hey, hey! You were one of the Seven Warlords?!
No wonder you're so strong!
Forgive me. I should have introduced myself sooner.
It's surprising you didn't know...
Hey! What do you mean, “Navy HQ”?!
You better not be saying that this ship is heading for Navy HQ!
You know about the war between
the Navy and the Whitebeard Pirates, right?!
Uh, what?
Navy HQ?
What are you saying?
It's not our fault that you're so dim-witted.
What?!
Now that we're through the Gates of Justice, the only possible destinations are Enies Lobby and Navy HQ.
Mary Geoise
Enies Lobby
Navy Headquarters
(Marineford)
The Great Prison
Impel Down
We're currently traveling the government's exclusive route, the Tarai Current.
This is an enormous vortex that connects the government's three main facilities.
The only reason we escaped in the first place was because we wanted to join the battle.
Yeah, the real fight starts now!
“The real fight starts now?!”
N-Nobody told us about this!
Stop the ship right now, damn you!
Stop it!
We're already riding the current.
There's no way for me to stop it!
Why don't you two just get off?
-Ok, goodbye!
-Bye!
You really think we'll get off?!
We're both devil fruit users! We'd drown!
The Navy high command and the Warlords versus the Whitebeard Pirates... this war is scary as hell!
If that's where we're going, I'd rather go back to prison!
All of us from 'Kama Land knew about this.
Hey, can you hear something?
M-Maybe we should pretend we're not here?
Uh, hello?
He answered!
This is Navy HQ.
Yeah, this is Luffy.
Don't tell him your name! You're a pirate!
We received word from Impel Down security
that a group of escapees commandeered a ship.
Judging from the information we received before we lost contact with Impel Down,
we've determined that there are two ringleaders behind this breakout.
Two?
The pirate Straw Hat Luffy,
and his fellow pirate...
Buggy the Clown.
-Huh?!
-W-What?!
Seriously?!
They're treating Captain Buggy as a bigger threat than the warlords?!
Who are you?!
Why me?
Hand me the papers.
Yes, sir. Here they are.
We've underestimated you in the past.
We assumed you were just some upstart pirate.
Buggy the Clown, we never would have guessed
that you were a former crewmate of the pirate king, Gold Roger.
How'd they find out?!
You were on the Oro Jackson?!
This is huge!
A-A star! He's a pirate star!
We've also received word that you are like a brother to Red-Haired Shanks of the Four Emperors.
What did you say?!
I'm impressed that a man of your caliber was able to lie low until now.
We won't underestimate you,
now that you've come this far.
Uh, no...
We've yet to find any connection between you and Fire Fist Ace...
but I'm sure your objective is the same as Straw Hat Luffy's: to save Ace.
We've also confirmed that Jinbe, Crocodile, Ivankov,
as well as over 200 other escapees, are on board the ship.
I'm warning you all now...
Unless we open the Gates of Justice,
you will not be able to reach Marineford,
nor will you be able to escape from the Tarai Current.
None of you have any chance of escape.
You'd better resign yourselves to that.
That is all.
Hey, wait, Navy!
I'm definitely going to save Ace!
I'll put your potatoes on a platter!
Potatoes...?
“Heads!” It's “heads on a platter,” Straw Hat-san!
Like this is any time to be preparing potatoes!
Hey, why is this guy picking a fight with Navy HQ anyway?
No, wait! More importantly, Captain Buggy,
you were a member of the pirate king's crew?!
And you're also like a brother to Red Hair?!
Our savior is truly one amazing pirate!
No, wait!
Oh, crap! Now that they know,
the government will start hunting me!
Well, I never expected him to have that kind of past.
And despite that, he's so weak.
But then, how can he be such a coward?
There's at least one black sheep on every ship.
Shut up!
Now that you mention it...
If you're from the East Blue, then maybe you know a pirate named Buggy as well?
That old first mate guy mentioned something about this, too.
Huh? The first mate?
An old guy named Rayleigh. You know him, right?
What?! You met Rayleigh-san?!
Oh, that takes me back! The first mate, huh?
Where'd you meet him?
Dark King Rayleigh's name came up!
What an incredible conversation!
Captain Buggy! You truly are a dangerous man!
No, no!
Wait a second!
I mean, that's true and all,
but compared to those big shots,
the life I've led up till now is just...
You're amazing! You were a member of that legendary pirate crew!
Buggy! Buggy!
You idiots!
Quit cheering! I was technically just an apprentice!
You may be grateful to me for freeing you, but...
No, I'm telling you, you've got it wrong!
Well, not all of it is wrong.
Right! Wait a second...
It's true that the Navy has
overestimated me, but this could be a good thing!
That's right! Nothing they said was a lie!
There's no doubt that my reputation has grown!
If, by chance, someone...
like me...
manages to kill Whitebeard today, then I could become one of...
the Four Emperors?!
No, no, no, more than that...
I could become king of the pirates!
That's right! These escapees all have higher bounties than me!
I could put them to good use!
I can do it!
Captain Buggy! We will follow you wherever you go!
Just give the order! We'll steal the ship from the guys who wanna go to Navy HQ!
And then we'll be free!
Now, Straw Hat...
how about handing this ship over to us?!
We finally escaped! You think we'll go to Navy HQ?!
We've got Captain Buggy on our side!
We're counting on ya, Captain Buggy!
Buggy! Buggy!
Such a nuisance...
We'll just have to kill them all.
Yeah, I'm starting to feel like I can do this!
Buggy! Buggy!
Be silent, you brazen idiots!
You're letting your emotions run away with you.
This ship won't stop!
It's headed straight for the battlefield!
And we're all on board.
Just think about it!
We're within arm's reach of the summit,
where the best of the best are!
We won't get another chance like this again in our lifetimes.
If you're real men, won't you come with me and fulfill your dreams?
Today, I will take Whitebeard's head, and with it, the whole world!
Yeah! Captain Buggy!
Captain Buggy!
We were plunged into the darkest depths of hell.
At some point, we lost something important!
We used to have it! That inner gem known as dreams!
We'll follow you to the ends of the world!
Who needs a peaceful life anyway?!
That's right! Let's go, men!
To Navy HQ!
Buggy! Buggy!
Looks like they've come to an agreement.
He seems to have a talent for convincing people, at least.
Captain Buggy, you're one of the world's real trailblazers!
We'll follow you anywhere!
Go ahead and follow me!
Just do whatever vyou want.
On the same island as Navy HQ, Marineford,
there is a large town where mainly the marines' families reside.
All those citizens have been ordered to evacuate.
From their new haven in Sabaody Archipelago,
the people eagerly watch the execution via monitors.
Reporters and cameramen have
gathered from all over the world
to watch and keep the rest of the world informed.
Navy HQ has put all their forces into this.
Of course. And I'm sure Whitebeard knows.
So, will he really show?
All scouting ships dispatched by the Navy have been sunk.
Nobody has seen any trace of Whitebeard,
and the tension at Marineford keeps building.
Less than three hours remain before the execution.
Go up the stairs.
Listen, Luffy!
We have to live our lives without regrets!
Yeah!
Someday, we'll head out to sea,
and then we'll be able to do whatever we want!
No one will have more freedom than us!
The South Blue
Three hours to go. I wonder if
Whitebeard's already shown himself?
Who knows. Are you sure he'll show?
Even if this is Whitebeard,
he's gotten pretty old by now, right?
You think?
He's a relic from before the Great Pirate Era.
He's probably gone senile by now.
He's been quiet these last few years.
The East Blue
He's been around for ages.
Can the Navy high command be defeated?
Regardless of who wins,
there's going to be heavy casualties.
It'd be best if he didn't show,
and the execution went ahead without incident.
The North Blue
Hey! Hey! I want some booze, old man!
You think I'm gonna open the pub on a day like this?!
War might break out, you know!
Go home! If the world's still here tomorrow, I'll open the pub then!
Then please, just sell me some booze!
It feels like we're the ones facing execution here!
We gotta have a drink to endure this!
Don't think of him as just some old guy; he's as strong as ever.
The West Blue
We saw him a year ago, and he was just sitting there.
We lost all hope that we would survive.
The Grand Line
Is Whitebeard really such a terrifying pirate?
Even the kids know.
They're singing about him while jumping rope.
♪ The pirate, Whitebeard, scarier than the devil! ♪
Dear Lord,
where is this world headed?
Navy Headquarters
Marineford, The Grand Line
Hurry and get ready!
You! Move it!
Show no fear!
Whatever happens, only three hours remain.
Then all of this will be over!
In all, more than 100,000 marines
have gathered from all over the world.
Fifty battleships encircle the crescent-shaped bay.
And within the bay, countless cannons are ready.
The front row of the troops
can be seen from the port.
Among them are the five rogues that could decide the outcome of this war,
the members of the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
Below the execution platform, Navy HQ's most powerful combat force stands guard:
the three Navy admirals!
Navy Admiral
“Aokiji” Kuzan
“Akainu” Sakazuki
Navy Admiral
“Kizaru” Borsalino
Now,
all the world's forces of justice...
await the Whitebeard Pirates...
to prevent them from rescuing Ace.
I see it!
Hey! Jinbe!
I can see the Gate of Justice!
That was fast!
No, we're actually pretty late!
If the wind had been more favorable, we would have arrived sooner!
So, how are we going to get through that gate?
My men! It's almost time!
Time for what?
Time for Captain Buggy to take over the world!
That's right, my comrades!
Who cares about Navy HQ?!
Hey, look! There's Fire Fist Ace!
That's the man that could trigger this world-changing war!
The fate of the world depends on him!
I'm gonna tell them everything, Garp.
Do whatever you want. I'll be down there.
Stand down.
Yes, sir!
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
What's happening?
Give me the transponder snail.
Yes, sir.
I have an announcement for you all.
Portgas D. Ace...
The execution of this man is of paramount importance.
You've done nothing wrong.
Women always get sympathetic at times like this, Tsuru-chan.
Ace. What is your father's name?!
His father?
What's this all about?
My father is Whitebeard.
Not true!
It is! Whitebeard is the only father I have!
Years ago, we dedicated a lot of manpower to following his movements.
We suspected that man might have conceived a child on a certain island.
We relied entirely on Cipher Pol's vague information about this possibility.
Newborns...
The unborn...
We investigated every possible infant and their mothers but we found nothing.
But I suppose that was to be expected.
Your mother risked her life to deliver you safely.
She performed a special trick.
She deceived us...
No, she deceived the whole world!
She lived on an island called Baterilla, in the South Blue.
Her name was Portgas D. Rouge.
Your mother used her sheer willpower to pull off something unimaginable.
She carried her child in her womb for 20 whole months.
What is he saying?
She used all of her strength
and died as soon as she gave birth to you.
And so a year and three months after the father's death,
a child was born, carrying the blood of the most evil man in the world.
That child was you!
I'm sure you already know...
A newborn bears no sin.
Garp.
Take care of my child.
Your father is...
the pirate king, Gold Roger!
Editing, Sewil
Quality Control, Galaxy 9000, Grug, Pepperjack
Timing, Galaxy 9000
Translation, Yibis
Visual Effects, Datenshi, KaitouYahiko
Graphics, Datenshi
Karaoke, KaitouYahiko
Soundtracking, Halee
Raws, df68